Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Building Drawings and Large-Format Materials OS
New York University Archives
- Series VIII: Posters and Event Fliers, 222487
  - Presentations, movie screenings, musical events, etc., 1988-2001; 222494 (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Sports events, lectures, music, some posters signed by performer, etc. (3 folders), circa 1980s-1990s; 222493 (Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Organizational charts for NYU in general, School of Engineering, University Development, and School of Education departments, 1920-1930; 222492 (Box 18)
  - Silver Jubilee party for fraternities; Strike Coordinating Committee; anti-Vietnam; Sesquicentennial Celebration; Emily Warren Roebling dedication; etc., 1932, 1969-1983; 222491 (Box 18)
  - Humanities Council events/seminar posters, 1973-1986; 222490 (Box 18)
  - Humanities Council posters for various events, 1973-1990; 222488 (Box 18)
  - Humanities Council posters for various events: seminars, etc., 1979-2000; 222489 (Box 18)
  - 91st Washington Square Outdoor Art Exhibit, 1977; 222496 (Box 20)
  - Posters and Event Fliers, 223903 (Box 3)
  - Posters and Event Fliers, 223904 (Box 4)
  - Posters and Event Fliers, 223905 (Box 5)
  - Glee Club poster and event announcements, 1958, 1961, 1963 (Box 18)
  - Citizen Involvement in Urban Affairs HUD/NYU Summer Study poster, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Music concerts, comedy shows, movie screenings, NYU anniversary, etc. Some posters signed by performers, circa 1980s-1990s (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Reproductions of NYU buildings, landmarks, and events. Also, posters for concerts, shows, movies, and lectures (3 folders), circa 1980s-1990s (Flat-file-folder 1, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 3)
  - LIbrary-related poster, certificates of honor for NYU libraries, 1985-1990 (Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Concerts, movie screenings, Women's History month, anniversary events, lectures, etc., 1970s-1990s (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Educational and Cultural Alliance, 1977-83, undated (Flat-file-folder 4)
  - Concert posters: NYU Choral Arts Society and Glee Club, 1975, undated (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Protest Vietnam sign, advertising posters for NYU sports, events, 1970s-1990s (Flat-file-folder 2)
  - Bobcat (Library Catalog) Poster, circa 1980s (Flat-file-folder 3)